<DOC>
<DOCNO>LEMONDE94-002380-19940420</DOCNO>
<DOCID>LEMONDE94-002380-19940420</DOCID>
<ACCOUNT>333369</ACCOUNT>
<DATE>19940420</DATE>
<LMDOC>RIP</LMDOC>
<FAB>04199000</FAB>
<SUBJECTS>DECORATION HONORIFIQUE,1994,LISTE,MUTATION</SUBJECTS>
<PUM1>QUO</PUM1>
<REFERENCE1>2-026-01</REFERENCE1>
<SEC1>IPC</SEC1>
<PAGE>233</PAGE>
<TITLE>LEGION D'HONNEUR&gt; Défense</TITLE>
<TEXT>Sont promus commandeurs :</TEXT>
<TEXT>  Louis Challéat, Pierre Charié-Marsaines ; Victor Chaudrut, Jacques 
Leplomb, Lucien Loustalot, Paul Millet, Roger Philippon, Joseph Geis 
de Guyon de Pampelonne (de), Yves Arguillère, Jean Caralp, Henri 
Cuvillier, Gérard Dupont, René Faure, Gilbert Gabillot, Louis 
Misseri, Paul Rolland, Pierre Santus, Louis Stien, Jean Tréhiou, 
André Ternoir, Jacques Restoux, Joseph Sasia, Jacques Bonfils, Hocine 
Deffous, Raymond Lorho, Maurice Albord, Gustave Barlot, Louis 
Bellini, Adolphe Bennezon, Roger Bertrand, Joseph Dennu, Charles 
Gérard-Deprez, Léon Johnson, Bernard Hay.</TEXT>
<TEXT>
  Sont promus officiers :</TEXT>
<TEXT>
  Marcel André, Marcel Archambaud, Guy Borg, Lucien Bourgogne, 
Camille Dala, Gérard Figuié, Serge Galland, Paul Grégoire, Marcel 
Moll, Marcel Nivlet, Jean-Baptiste Patrone, Roger Pi, Elie Salin, 
Jean-Baptiste Tarillon, Joseph Tréguer, Robert Truche, Michel Faure, 
Nicolas Manick, Louis Delarue, Louis Bouvet, Gérard Clément, Eugène 
Javaudin, Georges Lavernhe, Jean Sabatier, Guy Pontoizeau, Jacques 
Augereau, Gilbert Bédos, Robert Béthery, Jean Blanchard, Roland 
Bontron, Pierre Chemin, Jean-Marie Chotin, Maurice Clerc, Jacques 
Cordeboeuf, Jean-Claude Dalle, Jean Delmas, Jean-Hubert Denys, Benoît 
Dubost, Jacques Ducloux, Stanislas Dutheil de la Rochère, Robert 
Fabritius, Jacques Feig, Jean-Jacques Foubert, François Froger, 
Pierre Gautier, Paul Grangeneuve, Manuel Guerrero, Jean Guyaux, Alain 
Guyot, Roger Hamel, Horst Heitjohann, Bertrand Hilaire, Pierre 
Histrimont, Joseph Hittinger, Roger Huet, Marie Humann-Guilleminot, 
Antonin Jacob, Jean Jaeger, Arnaud Jouannique, Adrien Kergroach, 
Henri Labastie, Jacques Labat, René Lambeaux, Georges Laporte, 
François Latron, Louis Le Goff, Pierre Le Louer, Christian Le Masson, 
Gilbert Lecat, Adolphe Leccia, Roland Mangeon, Simon Mangeot, Maurice 
Mansuy, René Martinet, Albert Martinez, Auguste Maurier, Michel 
Mauriés, Georges Memvielle-Arrébou, Georges Midy, Hubert Morio, 
Jean-Loup Noël, Henri Noirot, Michel Oliot, Ernest Paramelle, Jean 
Pencenat, Louis Ragot, Roger Retali, Marcel Revol, Bernard Rolland de 
Chambaudoin d'Erceville, Jean Salaün, Marcel Sarti, Edmond Saunal, 
François Scarbonchi, Maurice Schneider, Robert Schreck, André Seban, 
André Servaux, Raymond Stéger, Charles Thépaut, Claude Véziat, Claude 
Elien, Hubert Gagelin, Marc de Gentile-Duquesne, Antoine Le Mintier 
de La Motte-Basse-Bellom, Daniel Mazoyer.</TEXT>
<TEXT>
  Louis Andro, Michel Baron, Bernard Bérard, Jacques Bobériether, 
Alexandre Bousseau, Roger Boutinot, Ernest Caparros, Michel Clérot, 
Gilbert Dou, André Enout, Norbert Fesselet, Bernard Haegel, André 
Iché, Pierre Lagèze, Raymond Ménara, Jean Noguellou, Marcel Willems, 
André Wursthorn.</TEXT>
<TEXT>
  Léon Bloch, Henri Deloupy, Jean-Marie Jespard, Albert Stihlé.</TEXT>
<TEXT>
  Jean Bosch, Georges Fortin, Monique de La Brosse.</TEXT>
<TEXT>
  Onésime Mallet. Joseph Seintés.</TEXT>
<TEXT>
  Octave Duparc, Charles Fourton, Vincent Maymard, Marc Perucca, 
André Riffaud, Paul Rocchi, Alain Van Valenberg.</TEXT>
<TEXT>
  André Beigneux, Jean Ferres, Raoul Gautier, Etienne Monneret, 
Victor Oden, André Patureaux, Joseph Wachowicz.</TEXT>
<TEXT>
 Sont nommés chevaliers :</TEXT>
<TEXT>
  André Depont, Maurice Lapouge, Jean Allard, Fernand Amin dit Belot, 
Yves Baranger, Mohamed Ben Djillali, Paul Besson, Marcel Bigard, Marc 
Bucherie, Gérard Cariou, Robert Coisy, Jean Dislaire, Pierre Dupont, 
Paul Eisenberg, Jean Foll, Pierre Garry, Jean Gobert, Jean-Pierre 
Guyot, Bernard Hilt, Jean Jaszczur, Louis Kermanet, André 
Kraszewoski, Bertrand Maréchaux, Robert Mariolan, Dante Mezzone, 
André Milani, Gavril Moldovan, Marcel Morvan, Ambroise Mouden, Roger 
Mouly, André Mudler, Joseph Musial, Louis Paillier, Jean Paoli, 
Marcel Perigot, Robert Prudent, André Rambeau, René Regeard, Roger 
Rousseau, Joseph Saint-Cast, François Sisti, Jean Terrisse, Michel 
Victor. Roland Gantin, Marcel Geffroy, Jean-Pierre Grolleau, Albert 
Igigabel, Jean Morvan, Henri Bonnefond, Robert Botto, Alexis Cordin, 
Eugène Criqui, Maurice Dudebout, Bernard Gaudineau, François Kerfant, 
Pierre Lalanne, Serge Muls, Alain Corazzini, Pierre Deregnieaux, Jean 
Dijols, Michel Dupuy, Pierre Madeuf, Jean-Claude Peguin, Maurice 
Robineau, Robert Ulmann, François-Xavier Donnadieu, Henri Albericci, 
Pierre Anckaert, Christian Andoque, Saïd Anouar, Henri Arsanto, Roger 
Bauer, Ali-Cherif Beljouani, Michel Berthé, Pierre Bonnet, Jean 
Chapel, Maurice Constant, Gérard Deboichet, Marcel Deillas, Guy 
Dougé, Jean Ducret, Jean-Pierre Dussaux, Julien Faisandier, Jacques 
Fleury, Jean Fradin, Emile Giron, Marcel Giudicelli, Rogerius Gysels, 
Gabriel Hanotaux, André Héral, Guy Hervo, Jean-Claude Houdin, Jean 
Hubert, Raymond Jacquet, Gaston (de) La Guerrande, Paul Le Maire, 
Daniel Léger, Yves Lemaire, Henri Leprat, Mihaly Marosvolgyi, René 
Martinetto, Daniel Martinez, Jean-Marie Mathieu, Jean Millour, 
Etienne Nicolas, Claude Pinault, Jean Poulvelarie, Jean Roussière, 
Fernand Schmidt, André Soler. Michel Tardif, François Teilhard de 
Chardin, Jean-Paul Ters, Paul-Louis Theynard, Marc d'Ussel, Raymond 
Voguin, Christian Giry, Jean Griesser, Marcel Mallet, Joseph Trélhu, 
André Batany, René Bisner, Henri Dumas de Champvallier, Michel Geay, 
Michel Genet, Jean Maire, Lucien Ménès, Jean Prat, André Saillard, 
Marcel Tricot, Gérard Charpentier, Pierre Collette, Alain Haertig, 
Yves Harel, Michel Jonquet, Jacques Kerisit, Denis Kints, Daniel 
Tisseyre.</TEXT>
<TEXT>
  Pierre Barats, Pierre Berceaux, Raoul Blay de Gaïx (de), Paul 
Courcier, Jean-Louis Fongue, Joseph Lopez, Roger Mizzi, Roger 
Patillaud, Augustin Séréni, Léonce Betton, Jean Canale, Raymonde 
Corneux, Eugène Guichard, Guy Souleyreau, Perla Szafrsztejn, 
Marie-Louise Timbal, Raymond Voisin, Thérèse Walgenwitz, Simonne 
Brisset, Ginette Dior, Louis Dujardin, Raoul Giquel, Raymond Jacgert, 
Jacques Malherbe, Amédée Thevenet, René Béthermin, Raymond Cazade, 
Pierre Chantrel, Pierre Compois, Michel Denisse, André Destelle, 
Roger Gaillard, Louis Gilbert, Georges Holveck, Louis Vanin, Joseph, 
Weiten, René Abily, Fernand Allard, Roger Alliot, Maurice Amzallag, 
Lucien Ancel, Antoine Baésa, Robert Barrier, Martial Berrier, Camille 
Bertheau, Gilbert Boisset, Jacques Bono, Laurent Boschel, Claude 
Bouillot, Jacques Brinbal, Marcel Brombeck, Vincent Brotons, Jean 
Brun, Alfred Canal, Victor Canut, Julien Castell, Albert Catherinet, 
Louis Catiau, Jean Cavard, robert Cerfontaine, Jean Champion, Desmond 
Comat, Auguste Coupeau, Georges Daniel, Jean Darde, Charles Deguine, 
Jacques Dejouy, Jean Descrains, Ammar Djerad, Alphonse Dupiré, Roger 
Dutilleul, Félix Gandolfo, Paul Gerbi, Joseph Gualter, Paul 
Guillaume, Joseph Guis, Jean-Pierre Laborderie, Marcel Laurain, 
Gilbert Leroy, Henri Marius, Pierre Mélinon, Guiseppe Moresco, 
Georges Mougel, André Mulier, Jean Orsini, Paul Pélissou, Aurélio 
Pénalver Véra, Edouard Perzinski, Lucien Picq, Bedros Pirlian, Robert 
Pouret, Michel Préveaudeau, René Prost, Henri Raucy, Pierre Rioblanc, 
André Romand, Hubert Roux, Antoine Sallustro Daniel Salomon, Jean 
Sauli, Jean Stacchini, Léon Tabet, Pierre Vescovali, Marcelle 
Vézinat, épouse Gay, Robert Viard, Bernard Vignes, Jean Volland, 
Roger Xuéreb.</TEXT>
<TEXT>
  Ange Alvarez, Jacques Brodu, Robert Cadec, Claude Caminade, Armelle 
Glain, Boris Holban, Alfred Lambert, Claude Leclercq, Auguste Le 
Guillou, Rita Manni, épouse Pottier, Hubert Masson, Marie, Medard, 
Christian Motté, Robert Moulin, Roger Pons, André Vialle.</TEXT>
<TEXT>
  Georges Ballini, Armand Baux, Georges Berthet, Maurice Beurtheret, 
Léon Contie, Marie-Thérèse Delaunay, Henri Duthy, Marie Elicot, 
Françoise Ferré épouse Torché, Emile Jacques, Robert Laporte-Corbier, 
Raymond Létondal, Jacques Macabiau, Achille Marchal, Maurice Michel, 
Marcel Piat, Henri Ritz, André Rivere, Guy Sarramagnan, Germain Séon, 
Gaston Thevenard                         
</TEXT>
</DOC>
